// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single
// 2. boolean | true/false | single
// 3. MAQs | Multiple Answers | multiple

import { Topic } from '.'

export const Q017: Topic = {
  topic: 'TOEIC Part 5',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 10,
  totalScore: 10,
  totalTime: 100,
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Ryofu Transport focuses ------ on meeting deadlines while keeping transportation costs low.',
      choices: ['heavier', 'heavily', 'heavy', 'heaviness'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['heavily'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題161-170/#q161',
    },
    {
      question: 'Ms. Smith has owned and operated ------ recycle store for more than five years.',
      choices: ['she', 'hers', 'her', 'herself'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['her'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題161-170/#q162',
    },
    {
      question: 'When cleaning the dishwasher, please follow the ------ in the instruction manual that came with the machine.',
      choices: ['committee', 'urgency', 'storage', 'procedure'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['procedure'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題161-170/#q163',
    },
    {
      question: 'With this software application, users can ------ process and edit digital images and photos.',
      choices: ['easy', 'ease', 'easily', 'easier'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['easily'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題161-170/#q164',
    },
    {
      question: '------ members of the press authorized by the management office are allowed to take pictures in the building.',
      choices: ['Because', 'Only', 'Due to', 'Until'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Only'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題161-170/#q165',
    },
    {
      question: 'If that machine ------ down, we would be able to ship the order by the end of this week.',
      choices: ['does not break', 'will not have broken', 'will not break', 'did not break'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['did not break'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題161-170/#q166',
    },
    {
      question: 'Employees at Wabon Construction responded ------ to the new salary structure and leave policy.',
      choices: ['favorably', 'favorable', 'favor', 'favoring'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['favorably'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題161-170/#q167',
    },
    {
      question: '------ the weather was nice last Saturday, there were fewer visitors to the outdoor concert than anticipated.',
      choices: ['Initially', 'Despite', 'Due to', 'Even though'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Even though'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題161-170/#q168',
    },
    {
      question: 'In an effort to increase its market share in the pharmaceutical industry, Hudson Chemicals announced that it will ------ with Browns Pharmaceutical.',
      choices: ['acquire', 'generate', 'merge', 'compile'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['merge'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題161-170/#q169',
    },
    {
      question: 'When ------ a lease agreement, you should consult with your supervisor first and obtain approval before doing so.',
      choices: ['revise', 'revising', 'revised', 'revises'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['revising'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題161-170/#q170',
    },
  ],
}